{
    "data":[
        {
            "question": "1. ______ is used to find and fix bugs in Java Programs.",
            "choices":["JVM","JRE","JDK","JDB"],
            "answer":"JDB"
        },
        {
            "question": "2. Arrays in java are-",
            "choices":["Object references","Objects","Primitve data types","None"],
            "answer":"Objects"
        },
        {
            "question": "3. Identify the modifier which can't be used for constructor.",
            "choices":["Public","Protected","Private","Static"],
            "answer":"Static"
        },
        {
            "question": "4. Java was first released in-",
            "choices":["1992","1995","1990","1996"],
            "answer":"1995"
        },
        {
            "question": "5. Earlier name of Java Programming language was -",
            "choices":["Eclipse","OAK","Netbean","J"],
            "answer":"OAK"
        },
        {
            "question": "6. Java Source Code is compiled into _____",
            "choices":[".obj","Source Code","Bytecode",".exe"],
            "answer":"Bytecode"
        },
        {
            "question": "7. HTML based Java Documentary help can be accessed using __________",
            "choices":["javahelp","javamanual","javadoc","none"],
            "answer":"javadoc"
        },
        {
            "question": "8. Which of the following is not a primitive data type ?",
            "choices":["byte","enum","short","int"],
            "answer":"enum"
        },
        {
            "question": "9. Which of the following is the smallest data type?",
            "choices":["int","byte","short","long"],
            "answer":"byte"
        },
        {
            "question": "10. Who is known as the Father of Java Programming Language?",
            "choices":["Bjarne Stroustrup","James Gosling","Gabe Logan Newell","Akio Morita"],
            "answer":"James Gosling"
        }
    ]
}